roadrouteindia.com 2017-06-06

# Road Route Map| Route Map India| Driving Directions| Shortest Route| Driving Distance| Route Planner| Distance Between

## Privacy Policy

Weat roadrouteindia.com are committed to protect personal information/data of our customers to maintain the privacy of their personal information, which may collect and provide our approach towards handling or dealing with the same. Its Privacy Policy describes the personal information, is designed and developed to address the privacy and security of your personal information provided to us. 

Fundamentally, "Personal information" is any piece of information that could be used to distinctively identify a person, contact him/her, or locate an individual, or could be used with information available from other sources to uniquely identify a user. For the purpose of this policy, your sensitive personal data or information has been given due consideration as a part of personal information. Your privacy is important to us. 

The personal information is purely used to analyze trends, study the site and track movement of users to gather broad demographic information for internal use. We have included links on this site for reference.We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. The contents of this statement may be altered at any time at our discretion.

Users of our site, www.roadroutemap.com, may be permitted to submit comment for publication in various areas of the website of road route map. You will be deemed to consent to these guidelines, and these terms and conditions, if you choose to post any comments to the site. We, or authorized third parties, reserve the right to refuse to publish, cut, crop or edit your content at our or their sole discretion. We may remove your content from use at any time. We warrant that the content you submit to us is not obscene, ominous, libelous, deceitful, harassing, misleading, offensive, invasive of another's privacy, defamatory of any person or otherwise illegal. 

Roadrouteindia.com reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time, as and when the need arises. We request you to visit our website www.roadroutemap.com periodically for contemporary information and changes.
